[{"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b28", "question": "Who wrote \"The Murders in the Rue Morgue\"?", "answer": "Edgar Allan Poe", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fd2cfb42596a59cbdfbd372", "question": "Who said, \u201cStrong minds discuss ideas, average minds discuss events, weak minds discuss people\"?", "answer": "Socrates", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d55", "question": "Which University did author J. K. Rowling graduate from?", "answer": "University of Exeter", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6d0", "question": "What is the more common name for the hormone epinephrine?", "answer": "Adrenalin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a150", "question": "What did Dorothy's house land on in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?", "answer": "The Wicked Witch of the East", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392bf", "question": "What was the British equivalent to the popular American MTV show \"Jersey Shore\"?", "answer": "Geordie Shore", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd822ccd0de9af39e9d46ab", "question": "What is said to be the first table top game to exist?", "answer": "Dice", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd2d4aa2596a59cbdfbd3a6", "question": "What does bone marrow produce?", "answer": "Red and white blood cells, as well as platelets.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7da", "question": "What US president put a Twinkie in the country's millennium time capsule?", "answer": "Bill Clinton", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b11a", "question": "Along with Karl Marx, who wrote \"The Communist Manifesto\" in 1848?", "answer": "Frederich Engels", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ffd", "question": "Whose secretary was Loelia Ponsonby?", "answer": "James Bond's", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59e80658de59ea584496feb0", "question": "The character Smike appears in which Dickens novel?", "answer": "Nicholas Nickleby", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338de9", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"wok\"?", "answer": "Cantonese", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b151", "question": "In what year did Charles Lindburgh make his historic non-stop solo flight across the Atlantic?", "answer": "1927", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339586", "question": "In the movie \"Young Frankenstein\", who played the role of the old blind man who invited the Monster into his cottage?", "answer": "Gene Hackman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe69ae020565ad31a57c757", "question": "What was the first non-axis jet plane to see combat?", "answer": "Gloster Meteor", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff0b361e662d71a53650fde", "question": "Which novel starts with Colonel Aureliano facing a firing squad?", "answer": "\"One Hundred Years of Solitude\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a905", "question": "What major river runs through Vienna?", "answer": "Danube", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c067", "question": "With which Major League team did Randy Johnson make his 1988 debut?", "answer": "The Montreal Expos", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5c3e9952ebfabb9c85d8a971", "question": "Eirene was the Greek goddess of what?", "answer": "Peace", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339efa", "question": "Who won a 1991 best male vocalist Grammy despite having died in 1988?", "answer": "Roy Orbison", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60121b8063c99d48cd169b0e", "question": "\"Cartomancy\" tells the future using what?", "answer": "Playing cards -- Like tarot reading, cartomancy involves the use of cards. Instead of using tarot cards, playing cards are used.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe76fa4eec85e375820b2ed", "question": "What is the largest city in Switzerland?", "answer": "Zurich", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398dc", "question": "What was the name of the Cartwright's ranch on the TV show \"Bonanza\"?", "answer": "Ponderosa", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58b8d4d22b42d4a3561a9efc", "question": "In the comic book series \"Strangers in Paradise\", which employee of Mrs. Parker was framed with stealing $850,000 from Senator Chalmers?", "answer": "Samantha", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5906834bff9c0647b50a80a5", "question": "What TV show, sequel to an ABC sitcom that ended in 1995, was released by Netflix on February 26, 2016?", "answer": "Fuller House", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fc8424f78d18506ae1fe48b", "question": "In the Western Hemisphere, what is the most western capital?", "answer": "Mexico City", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c47a", "question": "In what year was the Toyota Prius hybrid car first commercially sold?", "answer": "1997", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339902", "question": "What was the first Top 40 hit for Tom Petty & The Heartbreakers?", "answer": "Breakdown", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b1a401dd7bf43be5e793", "question": "What was the original name of the Popsicle?", "answer": "Eppsicles (Eppsicle was named after its creator, Frank Epperson.)", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aefe", "question": "What treaty ended the American Revolution?", "answer": "Treaty of Paris", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2c5", "question": "Whose military textbook \"Infantry Attacks\" was read, famously by George Patton?", "answer": "Erwin Rommel's", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fed2bd0ec223966ae8f8913", "question": "In the film \"Dances with Wolves,\" what happens to Dunbar's diary?", "answer": "It's used as toilet paper.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcec", "question": "What Internet search engine runs the Babel Fish translation service?", "answer": "AltaVista", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a073", "question": "In the film \"Saving Private Ryan\" what was Private Ryan's first name?", "answer": "James", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60173e3544491cbd7c5a17ae", "question": "According to U.S. history, which is the \"date which will live in infamy\"?", "answer": "Dec. 7, 1941 -- The date the U.S. naval base, Pearl Harbor, was the target of a devastating surprise attack by Japanese forces.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b097", "question": "In what decade was NATO formed?", "answer": "1940s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339090", "question": "In Greek mythology, who was the god of the underworld?", "answer": "Hades", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c07f", "question": "What is the fear of horses called?", "answer": "Equinophobia or hippophobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea31ebff048f679a45aae6", "question": "What was invented by Chinese astronomer and mathematician Chang Heng?", "answer": "The first seismograph", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133976b", "question": "Who directed both his father and his daughter to an Oscar?", "answer": "John Huston", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c479", "question": "Who founded Microsoft with Bill Gates in 1975?", "answer": "Paul Allen", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d5a", "question": "Where was Wonder Woman born?", "answer": "Paradise Island", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b31c", "question": "Who was the 13th President of the United States of America?", "answer": "Millard Fillmore", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc16", "question": "What are the official United Nations languages?", "answer": "Arabic, Chinese, English, French, Russian and Spanish", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaef", "question": "Which ocean does Tanzania have water access to?", "answer": "Indian", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbaf", "question": "In karate, what color belt is earned just before black?", "answer": "Brown", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba5f", "question": "In what Missouri town did Mark Twain grow up?", "answer": "Hannibal", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adab", "question": "The \"Harappan Civilization\" is also known by what other name?", "answer": "Indus Valley Civilization", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6014c6e0fbde8045e48466bb", "question": "How is Lyme disease transmitted?", "answer": "The bite of blacklegged ticks infected with the bacterium\u00a0Borrelia burgdorferi\u00a0or rarely,\u00a0the bacterium Borrelia mayonii.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339eff", "question": "What famous horse belonged to Dudley Do-Right?", "answer": "Horse", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b113", "question": "What is the better known name of the Spanish mission San Antonio de Valero?", "answer": "The Alamo", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b358b175db0d66a186cb555", "question": "What is the name of the album for which Kendrick Lamar won the 2018 Pulitzer Prize for Music?", "answer": "\"DAMN.\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a456", "question": "How many provinces are there in Canada?", "answer": "10", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca06", "question": "What is the Shaddock a variety of?", "answer": "Citrus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391b0", "question": "Who played the role of Andy Dufresne in the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\"?", "answer": "Tim Robbins", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7cc", "question": "What is a traditional karate uniform called?", "answer": "Gi", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a5e", "question": "Jazz musicians sometimes refer to which instrument as a \"licorice stick\"?", "answer": "Clarinet", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff7c3082b316f4693fb67a5", "question": "In 2004, NYC took legal action against vendors at an Ecuadorian festival to prevent them from selling the meat of which animal?", "answer": "Guinea Pigs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59029d38cad1ec93f27df74b", "question": "What is Kahlua flavored with?", "answer": "Coffee", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe0dc07fcbed638185eaa0b", "question": "Where was the first Disney theme park outside the U.S. built?", "answer": "Tokyo", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394ba", "question": "What \"Twilight Zone\" writer also created \"The New People\" in 1969?", "answer": "Rod Serling", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b71", "question": "What comic strip did Scott Adams create while working for Pacific Bell?", "answer": "Dilbert", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba88", "question": "Whose death is described in the last chapter of the Torah?", "answer": "Moses", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fefc3cd6ce05a3942286f27", "question": "John Richard Baldwin is the birth name for what famous rock musician?", "answer": "John Paul Jones", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1a1", "question": "In France what is a Framboise?", "answer": "Raspberry", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f42", "question": "Who created the character of Yogi Bear?", "answer": "William Hanna and Joseph Barbera", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339947", "question": "Before becoming James Bond, Pierce Brosnan starred for five years on what TV series?", "answer": "Remington Steele", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58f5660b33a95c66dc4fe75d", "question": "Which British opera festival was started in 1934?", "answer": "Glyndebourne", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133957e", "question": "What game was played for money by the Vietnamese in \"The Deer Hunter\" movie?", "answer": "Russian Roulette", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a69d", "question": "The Shenandoah Valley is located in which eastern US state?", "answer": "Virginia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a599", "question": "What old Massachusetts town is nicknamed \"Witch city\"?", "answer": "Salem", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad2b", "question": "According to legend, what laws were so named because of the color of the paper used when the ordinance was written?", "answer": "Blue laws", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389eb", "question": "What major comedy star played Garp in the movie adaptation of John Irvning's \"The World According to Garp\"?", "answer": "Robin Williams", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd0d", "question": "What was the original brand of cereal whose mascot was Crazy Craving?", "answer": "Honeycomb", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc8f", "question": "Which stroke is swum first in a \"medley\" swimming event?", "answer": "Butterfly", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a069", "question": "Anna Maria Louisa Italiano changed her name to what?", "answer": "Anne Bancroft", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "597cd41ee347d002c297e4ad", "question": "How many years did Nelson Mandela spend in prison?", "answer": "27 Years", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8ee", "question": "Which letter stands for the Roman number 50?", "answer": "L", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c309", "question": "How many bones are there in the human body?", "answer": "206", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5febd6f97e83c707845b2170", "question": "When was the first year the three-point shot was introduced to the NBA?", "answer": "1979", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fede34d6ce05a3942286dd1", "question": "Who was originally cast as Holly Golightly in \"Breakfast at Tiffany\u2019s\"?", "answer": "Marilyn Monroe", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59008b61cf842fa4c4ba9698", "question": "How was American comedian and actor, William Claude Dukenfield, better known as?", "answer": "WC Fields\u00a0", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fc2f1a7cee580c7f8fd1e51", "question": "Who said, \"You only live once, but if you do it right, once is good enough.\"?", "answer": "Mae West", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b77b", "question": "What 1990's fad involved something known as a slammer?", "answer": "Pogs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdce", "question": "What star small forward is the father of NBA brothers Scooter, Drew, Jon, and Brent?", "answer": "Rick Barry", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395e1", "question": "In The Simpsons, who said: \"That horse better win, or we're taking a trip to the glue factory...and he won't get to come!\"?", "answer": "Homer Simpson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a999", "question": "In what country would you find the active volcano \"Pelee\"?", "answer": "Martinique", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b375", "question": "Who was the first female American in space?", "answer": "Sally Ride", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b48a", "question": "Which country were the 1992 Summer Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "Spain", "category": "history"}, {"id": "591c3709815febcc896f926c", "question": "What city provided the setting for the 1970's TV show \"One Day at a Time\"?", "answer": "Indianapolis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394a6", "question": "In what city do The Simpsons live?", "answer": "Springfield", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fedde596ce05a3942286dad", "question": "Which 1990's NBA great was nicknamed \"the Admiral\"?", "answer": "Hall of Famer David Robinson", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd96e8b23c87fd04dd15e39", "question": "What year was the current American flag designed?", "answer": "1958", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395b2", "question": "What is Agnes Skinner's nickname for Seymour in The Simpsons TV show?", "answer": "Spanky", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "590683bdff9c0647b50a80aa", "question": "What company manufactured Google\u2019s Pixel phone?", "answer": "HTC", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339058", "question": "Who wrote the epic poem \"Aeneid\"?", "answer": "Virgil", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6f8", "question": "Which state is home to the Fort Apache Indian Reservation?", "answer": "Arizona", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9ce", "question": "What is the sternum more commonly known as?", "answer": "Breastbone", "category": "science"}, {"id": "600241cf4be4723ccac2217d", "question": "Which author wrote the \"Winnie-the-Pooh\" books?", "answer": "A.A. Milne", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b623", "question": "How many gigabytes of capacity did the first iPod have?", "answer": "Five", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aff8", "question": "What were the first names of explorers, Lewis and Clark?", "answer": "Meriwether and William", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392f7", "question": "In the movie \"Some Like It Hot\", who played the role of Sugar Kane Kowalczyk?", "answer": "Marilyn Monroe", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a54a", "question": "The mouth of what bay is located between Cape Charles and Cape Henry?", "answer": "Chesapeake Bay", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5937edc208d98002fdd633cb", "question": "What is the name of Beethoven's third symphony?", "answer": "The Eroica", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cb3", "question": "Which Smurf has a heart tattooed on each arm?", "answer": "Hefty Smurf", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e15", "question": "Under what pseudonym did Charles Dickens write his first books?", "answer": "Boz", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5a9e94cc7ccba3ffe45786d7", "question": "What year did the programming language \"COBOL\" first appear, before being standardized in 1968?", "answer": "1959", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba0c", "question": "What homerun hitter was nicknamed the \"Sultan of Swat\"?", "answer": "Babe Ruth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1bb", "question": "What color was Rudolph the Reindeer's nose?", "answer": "Red", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffa54ccc73aa70ea0b70b1f", "question": "In what country are April Fool's jokes climaxed with the saying \"Doroughe sizdah\"?", "answer": "Iran", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b40b", "question": "In what country was margarine first patented?", "answer": "France", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe8f43d01dd7bf43be5e820", "question": "TBD stands for what?", "answer": "To Be Determined", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ac7", "question": "What was E.T.'s favorite candy in the movie \"E.T.: The Extra Terrestrial\"?", "answer": "Reese's Pieces", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a162b32f01ec323f8491727", "question": "What is the name of Natalie Merchant's debut solo album after leaving 10000 Maniacs?", "answer": "Tigerlily", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59f9b787364247bf200fb873", "question": "Which famous tapestry commemorates the Norman conquest of England?", "answer": "The Bayeux Tapestry", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339530", "question": "What show begins with the line \"In a time of ancient gods, warlords and kings...\"?", "answer": "Xena: Warrior Princess", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a541", "question": "Which US state is home to Crater Lake National Park?", "answer": "Oregon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fefa6036ce05a3942286ec9", "question": "In the film \"Home Alone,\" what nickname for Harry and himself did Marv want to use?", "answer": "The Wet Bandits", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59ca3cd944f0f6af5b066635", "question": "Which sitcom featured Judd Hirsch, Andy Kaufman, Tony Danza and Danny Devito?", "answer": "Taxi", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5e4", "question": "Lemurs are found almost entirely on which isolated island?", "answer": "Madagascar", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b64c", "question": "What European car maker was purchased by VW in 1969?", "answer": "Audi", "category": "general"}, {"id": "601b4af249076251badbeabe", "question": "Ruby Bridges became the first Black student to do what?", "answer": "At six-years-old, Ruby Bridges was the first Black child to be integrated into an all-white school in New Orleans in 1960.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7cd", "question": "What is divided by the Cassini Division?", "answer": "Saturn's rings", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b20c", "question": "In which nation did the woven-yarn craft of \"God's eyes\" originate?", "answer": "Mexico", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffb68675dad637d903c8842", "question": "Which is the southernmost country in the European Union with no Mediterranean coastline?", "answer": "Portugal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a48d", "question": "By what name is the Thames known as it passes through Oxford?", "answer": "The Isis", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7ff", "question": "Mt. Rainier is one of sixteen volcanoes in the world that is classified as what?", "answer": "A Decade Volcano", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5cd", "question": "Buzzards Bay separates mainland Massachusetts from what land mass?", "answer": "Cape Cod", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe640bbae7e414034b5aea5", "question": "Who was the inventor of the first battery?", "answer": "Alessandro Volta", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ad7e6c9b24f84e0b9f9ffb3", "question": "In computing, what does HTTP stand for?", "answer": "Hypertext Transfer Protocol", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b640", "question": "What comes out of a hawsehole?", "answer": "Ship's cable", "category": "general"}, {"id": "601b4c0e49076251badbeacc", "question": "Who got married in the very first White House wedding?", "answer": "Dolley Madison\u2019s sister -- Lucy Payne Washington, the sister of First Lady Dolley Madison, married Thomas Todd in 1819.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58d1156e4fea7fe947a22266", "question": "In the 1975 novel \"The Moneychangers\", what is the name of Alex Vandervoort's wife?", "answer": "Celia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e9a", "question": "What movie did the villain Dr. Szell appear in?", "answer": "Marathon Man", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffb675c5dad637d903c883d", "question": "According to its former minister of tourism, which country is known abroad for its three Rs: reggae, romance and running?", "answer": "Jamaica", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "593c4becb8198b9a2b077967", "question": "In which of the \"Die Hard\" films does Samuel L. Jackson star in?", "answer": "Die Hard with a Vengence", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aee9", "question": "Which royal house consisted of Henry IV, Henry V and Henry VI?", "answer": "House of Lancaster", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4b3", "question": "A heptagon has how many sides?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394a5", "question": "In what century was the original Star Trek set?", "answer": "The 23rd century", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b11c", "question": "Which Greek island was the center of the Minoan civilization?", "answer": "Crete", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59ae9552574a5ce6b56b8253", "question": "Which river carved the Grand Canyon?", "answer": "Colorado River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caa7", "question": "A plague is a group of what insect?", "answer": "Locust", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0e6", "question": "Which TV series was narrated by Walter Winchell?", "answer": "The Untouchables", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd69fcd6c0f9723ab15cb2f", "question": "What was the first book sold on Amazon?", "answer": "\"Fluid Concepts And Creative Analogies\"", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c65a", "question": "Roadrunners are members of which family of bird?", "answer": "Cuckoos", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff6692552a821ff76ae8b09", "question": "Who was Abraham's second wife?", "answer": "According to Genesis 2:15, Abraham's second wife was Keturah.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59637289967692ea851899c0", "question": "Approximately what percentage of the jellyfish's body is made up of water?", "answer": "95%", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b249", "question": "Who took the throne in the \"Glorious Revolution\" of 1688?", "answer": "William and Mary", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf55", "question": "This drink is made from espresso coffee, hot milk and chocolate?", "answer": "Mocha", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338da7", "question": "What breed of dog is Snoopy?", "answer": "Beagle", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c53a", "question": "What does FM stand for?", "answer": "Frequency Modulation", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff2129431a458464a93c44a", "question": "If a person is shot with one of Cupid's lead-tipped arrows, what emotion do they feel?", "answer": "Repulsion (The lead arrow makes the victim loathe and want to get away from the first person they see.)", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd9734b23c87fd04dd15e58", "question": "Who was the first person to single-handedly sail around the world?", "answer": "Joshua Slocum", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fec8bb1ec223966ae8f8841", "question": "What year was the first Super Bowl played?", "answer": "1967", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea3e5cff048f679a45ab5a", "question": "What disease does an endocrinologist generally study?", "answer": "Diabetes", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c795", "question": "What type of information does a DNA molecule carry?", "answer": "Genetic", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab0b", "question": "What is the capital of Guam?", "answer": "Hagatna", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b011", "question": "At the time the US was celebrating its bi-centennial who was the President?", "answer": "Gerald Ford", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe8f29901dd7bf43be5e811", "question": "What is the process of raising silkworms and making silk called?", "answer": "Sericulture", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe76643eec85e375820b27d", "question": "In which mountain range is the highest continuous paved road in the U.S.?", "answer": "Rocky Mountains", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a562", "question": "The Gila River flows into what river?", "answer": "Colorado River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a761", "question": "In which US city will you find Louis Armstrong International Airport?", "answer": "New Orleans", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59c1cedb7bd84c0ea43ad43c", "question": "Who played the best friend of Sarah Jessica Parker in the 1985 film \"Girls Just Wanna Have Fun\"?", "answer": "Helen Hunt", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1e7", "question": "Who is more commonly known as the Michelin Man?", "answer": "Bibendum", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9ec", "question": "The Kung San people live in what area of Africa?", "answer": "Kalahari Desert in Botswana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ac3", "question": "Joe Cool is an alter ego of which comic strip character?", "answer": "Snoopy", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe90a9401dd7bf43be5e89d", "question": "In 1901, Guglielmo Marconi received the first transatlantic wireless signal from atop Signal Hill in which city?", "answer": "St. John's, Newfoundland", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd66c5da5bfecdd737e0893", "question": "What was the name of the world\u2019s last passenger pigeon?", "answer": "Martha", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6015e1d6fe83fe1f2a824b99", "question": "What was the \"The Blitz\"?", "answer": "A term used for Germany\u2019s bombing campaign on London", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a065", "question": "According to the song what did my true love give to me on the fifth day of Christmas?", "answer": "Five gold rings", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133baf6", "question": "What sporting event is also called \"birling\"?", "answer": "Log rolling", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5901d794709c1c34536e6ea3", "question": "What was the first flavor of the malt beverage named \"Zima\"?", "answer": "Lemon-Lime", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe9f621ff048f679a45aada", "question": "What is the gestation period of a Hippopotamus?", "answer": "Eight months", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a262", "question": "What is the name of the summer camp in the \"Friday the 13th\" movie series?", "answer": "Camp Crystal Lake\u00a0", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad3b", "question": "In 1947, what pilot first broke the supersonic barrier?", "answer": "Chuck Yeager", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58f16accf7c52aae91cc07e1", "question": "Which state is home to Australia's highest mainland mountain?", "answer": "New South Wales", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c83a", "question": "What irrational number is the base of a natural logarithm?", "answer": "e", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5b7abc516490a8cc1a6e5299", "question": "What is the maximum high score that can be shown on the screen in the video game \"Pac-Man\"?", "answer": "999,990 points", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c87f", "question": "What kind of bird is an eider?", "answer": "A duck", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5c5", "question": "In cocktail terminology, what does \"neat\" mean?", "answer": "A drink poured without water, ice or mixers", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abd9", "question": "Lansing is the capital of which US state?", "answer": "Michigan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f031133890f", "question": "Who wrote \"Treasure Island\"?", "answer": "Robert Louis Stevenson", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc02", "question": "The name \"circus\" comes from what Greek word?", "answer": "Kirkos", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf51", "question": "What toy was released in 1958 creating an instant craze among children?", "answer": "The Hula Hoop", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb8b", "question": "In what city did NBA star LeBron James play his high school basketball home games?", "answer": "Akron, Ohio", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bf6", "question": "What US state was actress Julia Roberts born in?", "answer": "Georgia", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff516c5ff04d658268c92f4", "question": "Who was the first President to use the Oval Office?", "answer": "William Howard Taft", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2b9", "question": "Which of Henry VIII's wives was Anne Boleyn's cousin?", "answer": "Catherine Howard", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d1b", "question": "What German composer lost his hearing at the age of 20?", "answer": "Beethoven", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfe0", "question": "What is the fear of fur called?", "answer": "Doraphobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa01", "question": "What country celebrates its National Day on 17th May?", "answer": "Norway", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a682", "question": "Which states share a border with South Carolina?", "answer": "Georgia and North Carolina", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339407", "question": "Who played the role of Aileen in the 2003 movie \"Monster\"?", "answer": "Charlize Theron", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c560", "question": "What is the common name for a \"nitrous oxide\"?", "answer": "Laughing gas", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393bb", "question": "What was Robert De Niro's nickname in the movie \"Casino\"?", "answer": "Ace", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0ba", "question": "Who in the world of music and born 1984 has the real name\u00a0Victoria Christina Hesketh?", "answer": "Little Boots", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "595247c2736d4be723796b73", "question": "What is the name of Lady Antebellum\u2019s first #1 hit?", "answer": "\"I Run To You\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015e99ffe83fe1f2a824be9", "question": "In 1986, a U.S. court of appeals ruled that what magic-practising movement qualifies as a religion?", "answer": "Wicca", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3b9", "question": "In what decade was Montreal Canadien great Guy Lafleur born?", "answer": "1950s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6014c847fbde8045e48466d5", "question": "What kind of unique fur does a platypus have?", "answer": "As if it weren't an odd enough creature, the platypus' fur is bioluminescent, meaning they can glow in the dark.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b813", "question": "What is the Jewish New Year called?", "answer": "Rosh Hashanah", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7c987877e98cb977789f5", "question": "Which Pennsylvania town is the birthplace of \"Rolling Rock Beer\"?", "answer": "Latrobe", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9d1", "question": "What is the capital of the US state North Carolina?", "answer": "Raleigh", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f77", "question": "What was Gladys Knight's backing band?", "answer": "The Pips", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca42", "question": "Which vital organ does the adjective renal refer to?\u00a0", "answer": "Kidney\u00a0", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c166", "question": "Where might you drink Retsina\u00a0wine?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9a1", "question": "What does the \"c\" in the equation e=mc^2 stand for?", "answer": "Speed of light", "category": "science"}, {"id": "592ead43f83302ff91e46479", "question": "What is the fear of learning known as?", "answer": "Sophophobia", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c53c", "question": "What is the largest muscle in the human body?", "answer": "Gluteus Maximus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6015e4b4fe83fe1f2a824bb6", "question": "At what conference did the Allies set the terms for the Japanese surrender?", "answer": "The Potsdam Conference", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2d2", "question": "Who played the role of C.K. Dexter-Haven in the 1956 film \"High Society\"?", "answer": "Bing Crosby", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea7abbff048f679a45abee", "question": "Petrichor describes the scent of what?", "answer": "Outside after rainfall", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5aab2f4258d116dab4aecb48", "question": "What is racing driver's, Jean Alesi, birth name?", "answer": "Giovanni Alesi", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5cefc0ec948005ec986edce1", "question": "Who is the eighth member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Choerry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b358", "question": "What was the real name of the Boston Strangler?", "answer": "Albert DeSalvo", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b85e", "question": "In the financial industry, what does the abbreviation IMF stand for?", "answer": "International Monetary Fund", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4f6", "question": "St. Croix, St. John and St. Thomas are part of what US territory?", "answer": "Virgin Islands", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe4ed0d06d333868d34d769", "question": "What toy was originally created as a dog\u2019s chew toy?", "answer": "Rubber Duck", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fa7", "question": "Frank Zappa's 1979 album \"Sheik Yerboutti\" was a salute to what band's 1976 hit?", "answer": "KC and the Sunshine Band", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bacb", "question": "What is the International Criminal Police Organization better known as?", "answer": "Interpol", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339db1", "question": "In 1954, nuclear testing awoke what famous monster from the Pacific Ocean?", "answer": "Godzilla", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339311", "question": "In the movie \"Dirty Dancing\", what did Baby carry?", "answer": "A watermelon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab40", "question": "What place is also known as \"land nearest nowhere\"?", "answer": "Cape Three Points", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f04", "question": "What author created the character of Sherlock Holmes?", "answer": "Arthur Conan Doyle", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339873", "question": "In Disney's \"Alice in Wonderland\", who is the companion of The Walrus?", "answer": "A Carpenter", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c25", "question": "Who wrote the book \"One Fish, Two Fish, Red Fish, Blue Fish\"?", "answer": "Dr. Seuss", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff6690552a821ff76ae8b08", "question": "Who renamed the U.S. presidential yacht \"Honey Fritz,\" in honor of his grandfather, a former Boston mayor?", "answer": "President John F. Kennedy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "590087785304ceedb84e8997", "question": "Until World War II, solid blocks of what was commonly used as currency in Siberia?", "answer": "Tea", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a4c", "question": "The character Uriah Heep appeared in which Charles Dickens novel?", "answer": "David Copperfield", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58ab1a92baab681b09292195", "question": "What celebrity\u2019s car was fixed and raced in the 2009 documentary \u201cLove the Beast\u201d", "answer": "Eric Bana's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b109", "question": "What city hosted the 1992 Summer Olympics?", "answer": "Barcelona", "category": "history"}, {"id": "600782aebd51d85e222ab659", "question": "Who claimed he could \"drive away the devil with a fart\"?", "answer": "Martin Luther", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e09", "question": "Which of the Bront\u00eb sisters wrote only a single novel?", "answer": "Emily", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1ac", "question": "In 1978, which band asked \"Ever Fallen In Love\"?\u00a0", "answer": "The Buzzcocks", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391b1", "question": "Who played the female lead role in the 2007 movie \"Stardust\"?", "answer": "Claire Danes", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff516a8ff04d658268c92f2", "question": "What was America's first major fast food chain?", "answer": "White Castle", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59068335ff9c0647b50a80a4", "question": "Which artist received 2016 Grammy Award for \"Album of the Year\"?", "answer": "Taylor Swift", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398ec", "question": "Who played the title role in the 1984 film \u201cStarman\u201d?", "answer": "Jeff Bridges", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5be580c25415ba52ed6f0ab8", "question": "Doha is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Qatar", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b323268bf195a31e15d7390", "question": "What country is directly west of Spain?", "answer": "Portugal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6015e658fe83fe1f2a824bcb", "question": "Julius Caesar was assassinated on 15 March 44 BC, a date now often known by what term?", "answer": "Ides of March", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d53", "question": "How old was J. K. Rowling when she published the first Harry Potter book?", "answer": "31", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338903", "question": "What Ian Fleming novel's title is the nickname of the character Francisco Scaramanga?", "answer": "The Man with the Golden Gun", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a284", "question": "At which Canadian arena was Duran Duran's video for \"The Reflex\" filmed?", "answer": "Maple Leaf Gardens", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a621", "question": "Which US state was named after a president?", "answer": "Washington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339185", "question": "What TV show had the tagline: Most gripping sitcom since 1380?", "answer": "The Black Adder", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b56801dd7bf43be5e7d0", "question": "What does \"dachshund\" mean?", "answer": "Badger dog", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b59f", "question": "What does the \"Big Mac Index\" measure?", "answer": "Purchasing power parity between two currencies", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339de2", "question": "What \"Desperate Housewives\" creator broke into TV as a personal assistant to actress Dixie Carter?", "answer": "Marc Cherry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a8", "question": "What song is most famous for its suggestive chorus of \"Voulez-vous coucher avec moi (ce soir)\"?", "answer": "Lady Marmalade", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b690", "question": "The tuxedo got its name from what?", "answer": "A town in New York", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339184", "question": "What famous comedian played the vicar at the second wedding in the movie \"Four Weddings and a Funeral\"?", "answer": "Rowan Atkinson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6ce", "question": "Which one of your toes is also known as your \"hallux\"?", "answer": "Big toe", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b741", "question": "In the healthcare field, what does the abbreviation EMT stand for?", "answer": "Emergency Medical Technician", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bafb", "question": "What word is used to describe one and a half ounces of liquor?", "answer": "Jigger", "category": "general"}]